Meena Jim George

Web Developer



0481 107 418



meena_jim@yahoo.com



github.com/meenajim

PROFILE

I have recently returned to the IT industry after a 10 year career break raising my 2 kids. I used to work as a web developer in a university in Cyprus. I'm passionate about front end web development and I love getting along with people from different cultures. My goal is to immerse myself in front end web development and be part of a team that creates immersive web experiences.

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE 2018

General Assembly (GA)

MASTER OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY 2001-2004

Sikkim Manipal University

1998-2001 **BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (CHEMISTRY)**

Mahatma Gandhi University

EXPERTISE

Full stack web development, Front end development, Github, Heroku, Nokogiri, Cloudinary, Ruby gems,

PostgreSQL.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2007-2009 **European University**

WEB DEVELOPER

Administered the University's website and content management system. Worked with several university departments to gather content for the website and performed updates on the various portals of the

university

2004-2005 7CEES Group/Sun Infosys

TRAINEE

Various application were designed and developed using

VB.Net and SQL Server for several companies.

LANGUAGES

Ruby on Rails, Javascript, JQuery, React.JS, HTML, CSS (Bootstrap), Underscore, AJAX, SQL, Visual Basic.

PROJECTS PERFORMED

GA Projects

Tic Tac Toe Game (Javascript) Music School CRUD application (Full stack - Rails) Bike Sharing application (Full stack – Rails)

REFERENCES

Costas Papaconstantinou Director – Information Technology **European University** Contact: Available on request

Projects performed as part of degree course

Hospital Management System: (VB application interface

with MS Access Database)

Library Management System: (VB application interface

with Oracle 8i Database)